亲爱的
So, honey, this...
关于玩3P的事
...this threesome thing?
第三人  我们该从何找起
I mean, how are we even gonna start to find- - ?
我把我认识的女人中
Actually, l'm making a list of women l know
可能有兴趣的女人列了个表
who might be into doing this.
天啊
Boy.
有人有认真做功课哦
Someone's been doing their homework.
是啊  我知道我列了两次盖尔·罗斯坦
Yeah, l know Gail Rosten is in there twice...
但是她好...
...but she is so....
我知道
Oh, l know.
光是用讲的  就让我有点...
You know, just talking about it
有点...
is getting me kind of....
我也是
l know. Me too.
是吗  班已经睡了
l think Ben's asleep.
我觉得我们最好...
You know, l think it'll be better
-多储存精力  -有道理
- if we just save it. - Yeah.
也对  储存精力  没问题
Right. Save it. l can do that.
菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
好点了吗
How's it going?
我得离开这张床
l've got to get out of this bed.
我快疯掉了  疯掉了
l'm going crazy here! Crazy!
喝吧  宝贝
Here you go, sweetie.
这是什么  花草茶吗
What the hell is this, herbal tea?
我讨厌花草茶
l hate herbal tea.
-但我加了蜂蜜呢  -你喝才需要加
- Well, l put some honey in it.- You need honey in it.
她还不知道她被开除了  对吧
She doesn't know she was fired yet, does she?
对  医生说告诉她会害死她
No, the doctors say it may kill her.
你们两个女生在窃窃私语什么啊
What are you girls whispering about over there?
不过我觉得应该告诉她
But l think we should tell her.
它真是栩栩如生呀
l mean, it's just so realistic.
就是啊
l know.
他的名字叫拍拍
His name's Pat.
拍拍狗
Pat the dog.
我懂了
l get it!
你...
Are you...
你要再来一杯吗
Ready for a refill?
我不该再喝了...
l probably shouldn't.
所以我要喝
So l will!
-感觉好像下雨喔  -很酷吧
- lt's like it's raining. - Pretty cool, huh?
要是你以为把鱼扔进去
But if you think you could put a fish in there...
不会卡进机器里
...and it wouldn't get sucked into the mechanism,
那你就错了
you'd be wrong.
可以借用洗手间吗
Can l use your bathroom?
就在那里面
lt's right through there.
要是一个星期前
You know, l gotta tell you.
有人对我说
lf someone told me a week ago...
我会在乔伊·崔比安尼家撒尿...
...that l would be peeing in Joey Tribbiani's apartment....
人生真美好  对吧
Yeah. Life's pretty great, isn't it?
希望你饿了
l hope you're hungry.
我们先吃生蚝
We're starting with oysters.
你知道生蚝的作用吧
You know what they say about oysters, don't you?
有寄生虫吗
They have parasites?
不是
No...
有人说生蚝有催情作用
Some people say that oysters are an aphrodisiac.
-什么人说的  -就是人嘛
- What people? - People.
有人说的
People say it.
过来
Come here.
生蚝是吧
So, oysters, huh?
然后再吃一些中东的粉蒸羊肉
Then we'll have a little Middle Eastern couscous.
我们可以
Something we can eat...
用手抓着吃
...with our hands.
有意思
You know what's funny?
-我们学到传染病时...  -别别别
- When we were studying communicable diseases- - No, no. No, no.
这样才性感
lt's sensual.
-我都不知道  -好  好
- Didn't know. Okay. - Okay.
别啊 别啊
No, no!
讨厌  抱歉  医院找我
I'm sorry, sweetie, it's the hospital.
菜都很棒  帮我留点好吗
The food looks great. Save me some?
我可不敢保证哦
l can't promise anything.
我们是要来真的  对吧
We're really gonna do this, uh?
看样子是
Looks like it.
其实呢
You know what?
要是你觉得很怪  我们随时可以停...
lf this is too weird for you, you can still back out anytime- -
-我来开  -好
-l got it! - Okay.
苏珊  你好啊
Susan, hi.
谢谢你的加入
Thank you so much for coming.
我怎么可能错过呢
l wouldn't have missed it for the world.
我是罗斯
l'm Ross, by the way.
罗斯  你好
Hello, Ross.
-我喜欢你家的布置  -谢谢你
- l love what you've done with this space. - Thank you so much.
真火辣呀
How hot is this?!
可惜在这里的是我  不是罗杰
l'm sorry you're here with me instead of Roger.
就是啊
Yeah, me too.
我可以假装成他
Well, l could make it seem like he's here.
关于粉蒸羊肉的小常识
"Here's some little- known facts about couscous:
粉蒸羊肉以前不叫这个  直到1979年
They didn't add the second 'cous' until 1979."
别闹了  一点也不好笑
Stop it! That's not funny!
-好啦  -对不起  只是...
- Okay. - l'm sorry, okay? lt's just...
今晚原本应该是件大事的
tonight was supposed to be a big deal.
-今晚要干嘛  -你不会想知道
- What was tonight? - You don't want to know what tonight was.
好吧
Okay.
今晚要干嘛
What was tonight?
今晚本应该是我的初夜
Tonight was going to be my first time.
跟罗杰吗
With Roger?
不只是跟罗杰吗
Not just with Roger?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
别激动  "只做过四次先生"
All right, relax, Mr. l've-had-sex-four-times!
跟四个不同的女人呢
Four different women!
次数则是多太多了
l've had sex way more times.
-几次  -九次
- How many? - Nine.
我只是在等完美的对象
l'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
这样很好啊
Good, good for you.
你真的觉得罗杰是那个完美对象吗
You really think that Roger's the perfect guy?
不是  但他也不算糟
No, but he's not a horrible guy.
我都跟女人那样介绍自己
That's what l tell girls about me.
钱德勒  我会死于处女之身的
Chandler, l'm gonna die a virgin!
你不会  你又贴心又善良
No, you are not. You are sweet and wonderful...
你一定会"做"到的
and this is gonna happen for you.
是吗  什么时候
Oh, really? When?
-你想跟我做吗  -好啊
- Do you want to do it with me? - Okay.
我是开玩笑的
l was kidding.
我也是
So was l.
乔伊  你真是个了不起的演员
Joey, you're such an amazing actor.
你怎么在拉莫瑞医生
How do you know where Dr. Drake Ramoray leaves off...
跟乔伊·崔比安尼间转换的呢
...and Joey Tribbiani begins?
拉莫瑞医生
Well, with Dr. Drake...
有现成的台词
...they always tell me what to say.
而乔伊
And with Joey,
就得靠自己编话说了
l pretty much have to make it up on my own.
你告诉我...
Tell me something, Joey.
-我刚刚从沙发上摔下来  -没错
- l just fell right off the couch there. - Yeah, you did.
-我没事  -来  坐好
- Okay. - Come on, here you go.
我问你一件事
Let me ask you a question. Yeah.
上一次
When was the last time...
别人称赞你美丽  是多久以前了
...someone told you just how beautiful you are?
我的手麻了
l can't...I can't feel my hands.
来  手给我
Come on. Come here.
-我们不能这么做  -没错
- We can't do this. - No.
-吃生蚝吗  -好
- Oyster? - Yeah.
要是我们"做"了
lf... if we did do this,
我压力会很大
there'd be a lot of pressure on me, you know.
因为你等了这么久
Because you've waited a long time,
我不想让你失望
and l wouldn't want to disappoint you.
但是我没得比较啊
But you see, l have nothing to compare it to.
就算你很逊  我也不会知道啊
Even if you were horrible, how would l know?
这个想法不错
l do like that.
我压力更大
lt's harder for me.
得跟另外四个女人比
l have four women to compete with.
其实只有三个啦
Well, if it helps, there were only three.
-所以只有今晚对吧  -那当然
- So it'd just be for tonight, right? - Absolutely.
只是朋友在帮朋友的忙
lt would just be one friend helping out another friend.
别说了  不行
Stop it. We're not doing this.
-来做吧  -不行...
- Let's do it! - No!
-好吧  -好吧
- Okay! - Okay!
你有招数吗
Do you have any moves?
我是有几招啦
l have some moves.
-我没任何招  -没问题
- l have no moves.- Okay.
你在干什么啊
Okay, what you doing there?
对不起  真的太奇怪了
l'm sorry, this is just too weird.
是啊  还是算了
Yeah, let's just forget it.
-要是我关灯呢  -试试
- What if l turn out the lights? - Okay.
爽啊
Oh, yeah.
-钱德勒  -怎么了
-Chandler? - Yeah.
那是沙发
That's the couch.
天啊  太赞了
Oh, my God!
我知道
l know!
告诉你
l'll tell you something.
我们一定要再来一次
We are gonna do that again!
没问题
Okay.
早安
Morning.
-对喔  -没错
- Oh, right. - Yeah.
天啊
Oh, God.
居然让乔伊·崔比安尼  听到我吐的声音
Oh, l can't believe Joey Tribbiani heard me throw up.
-他还有看到一点呢  -不会吧
- He actually saw you a little bit too. - No.
天啊  我们没有...没有...
Oh, God, we...we didn't...?
没  没  没
No, no, no.
看完怎么可能有兴致
Not after seeing that.
我真是很糟糕
God, l'm just a horrible person.
-为什么  -因为我已经结婚了
- What? Why? - Because l'm married.
没错  我是有夫之妇
That's right, l'm a married woman.
还跑到一个电视明星家搞外遇
l came to a TV star's apartment to have an affair.
别傻了
That's ridiculous.
我才不是明星
l'm not a "star."
只是一般的名演员
l'm just a regular famous actor.
而我是个很糟糕的人
And l'm a horrible, horrible person.
瑞秋  你别再自责了
Rachel, will you stop saying that?
瞧
Hey, look.
你记不记得卡普丽丝临死前
Remember on the show when Capri was dying?
-给了我...  -石洞里的戒指  记得
- And she gave me--  - The ring from the cave. Yeah.
好...天啊  你可以留着它
Oh, my God! They let you keep that stuff?
当然  只要不被发现
Sure. As long as they don't find out,
想留什么都行
you can keep whatever you want.
我要把它送给你
And l want you to have it.
-不要...  -要
- No, l couldn't. - Yes, yes!
你每次看到它
Every time you look at it...
就要想起你是个好人
...l want you to remember that you are a good person, ok?
你有机会外遇
Now, you had the chance to cheat...
而且还是跟我
...and with me.
但是你没有
But you didn't.
这就是这枚戒指的意义
And that's what this ring stands for.
我以为它是代表
But l thought that ring stood for
卡普丽丝对哥哥永不止息的爱
Capri's undying love for her brother.
-你到底要不要  -我要
- Look, you want the ring or not? -Yes.
你醒了  太好了
Hey, look at you! You're up!
我想去走一走
l thought l'd try to take a walk.
你们帮我倒杯水  我马上回来
Will you pour me some water? l'll be back soon.
你不会是想打公共电话回公司吧
You're not gonna use the pay phone to call work, are you?
不是  我已经学到教训了
No. l've learned my lesson.
快点  动作快
Let's go! Come on! Move it!
菲比  动作快点
Phoebe, come on!
鞋子  公事包  谢了
Shoes, briefcase. Thanks, Lou.
祝你的胆囊早日康复
Good luck with the gallbladder.
乔伊
Hey, Joe, did...
你...你玩过3P吗
...did you ever have a threesome?
罗斯  我觉得卡萝很漂亮
Look, Ross, l think Carol's great,
我也相信你很有魅力  但是...
and l'm sure you're very attractive man, but....
不是  我之所以问你是因为...
No. The reason l'm asking is that...
我昨晚貌似玩了3P
...l sort of had one last night.
你  对
You? Yeah.
漂亮  如何  过瘾吗
All right. So? Was it amazing?
还...
lt was...lt was...
好啦
...okay.
只有还好  你的玩法对吗
Just okay? Did you do it right?
感觉就好像自己在参加派对时
Look, it's just, did you ever go to a party
觉得现场有我没我都一样
and think "would anyone really miss me if l weren't here?"
不过
But still, Ross...
跟两个女人玩得再难玩
...your worst day with two women,
-也胜过其他日子  你懂吧  -那当然
- pretty much better than any other day. - Oh, I know.
只是
lt's just...
我玩的部分很快就结束了
...my part seemed to be over pretty quickly...
然后我就一直在旁边等
...and then there was a lot of waiting around.
你跟她们两个都有做吧
But you got to be with both of them.
好像没有
Not really.
我只有跟卡萝做
Just Carol.
-另一个没有  -没有  她一直把我踹开
- Not the other one? - No, she kept kicking me away.
-那样很讨厌  -就是啊
- You don't want that. - No.
至少你饱了眼福
At least you got to see a lot of stuff.
的确是大饱眼福呀
Oh, l saw a lot of stuff.
-你后来有点无聊吧  -有一点
- You get a little bored? - A little.
还弄了点吃的
Made a snack.
-你弄了什么  -就是三明治
- What'd you have? - Just a sandwich.
火鸡肉  加一点芥末酱
Turkey. A little mustard.
-好像很赞  -是很赞
- Sounds good. - lt really was.
跟你分享一下我昨晚跟一个女生全垒打
Let me tell you about this chick l scored with last night.
等等  就是你嘛
Oh, no. Wait a minute, that was you.
哎哟  我成了荡妇了
Hey, check me out, I’m a slut!
晚上要不要找事情做
So you want to do something tonight?
不行  罗杰医生又要来了
l can't. Dr. Roger's coming over again.
也对
Oh, right, right.
因为你还在跟他交往
Because you're still seeing him,
他是个好人
and he's a good guy.
我记得有一次...
I mean l remember a time....
你还好吧
Are you okay?
好得很...
Yeah, totally.
很好  你呢
Totally. Are you?
棒呆了  真的好神奇
Great. lt's so amazing.
上次罗杰来的时候
Last time Dr. Roger came over,
我好紧张
l was so nervous.
但是跟你做过之后
But after being with you, l'm like,
我变成"医生轮到我了吗"
"Can the doctor see me now?"
那是当然
l bet he can.
"我没有预约
"You know l don't have an appointment,
不过现在来个体检  一定爽歪歪"
but l sure could use a physical."
你真的没事吗
You sure you're okay?
没事  别管我  我很好
Yeah, yeah. Don't worry about me, l'll be fine.
天啊  巴瑞
My God! Barry!
你说你周末都不在啊
You said you were going to be away all weekend!
没错  对不起  我回来早了
That's right! l'm sorry! l am early!
你们请继续
Finish, please!
惊喜  看看谁回来了
Surprise! Look who's back!
菲比
Hey, Pheebs!
通知警卫
Call security.
菲比  你不是被开除了吗
Pheebs, didn't you get fired?
我可不这么认为
l don't think so.
-菲比  -杰克
- Pheebe! - Jack! Hey!
-你来干什么  -我好多了  回来上班
- What are you doing here? - All better. Back to work.
但这个研究部猪头说我被开除了
This clown from research told me l was fired.
他应该好好研究嘛
He should do his research, huh?
你是被开除了
Well, you were fired.
才没有
No.
没有  我跟帮你接电话的人说了
l told that guy who answered your phone.
我没收到留言
l didn't get that message.
所以不算
So this doesn't count.
我先进办公室了
Anyway, l'll be in my office.
菲比  没有你的办公室
Phoebe, you don't have an office.
没关系  我就在这里工作吧
That's alright, l'll work right here.
这里很好  就在植物旁边
This is good. Next to this plant.
菲比  你听我说
Pheebe, listen...
你闯入我的办公室了
You're in my office.
听着  我替这家公司赚了很多钱
Look, l've made a lot of cash for this company. Okay?
而且是大钱
l am talking big bucks!
披索  日圆  卢布
Pesos! Yen! Rubles!
而我才犯了一个小错...
You make one little mistake- -
你损失了1千3百万元
You lost 1 3 million dollars.
原来一切都是为了钱啊
So now this is all about money?
我已经够...
You know, it's bad enough that....
别闹了吧
You have got to be kidding.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
-我心脏病又发作了  -什么
- l'm having another heart attack. - What?
我的心脏病又发作了
l'm having another heart attack!
叫救护车
Call 911 !
猪头
Dumb-ass!
菲比  你好吗
Pheebs, how's it going?
我被开除了  然后心脏病又发作了
They fired me, and l'm having a heart attack.
欢迎归队
Well, welcome back.
-罗斯  -瑞秋
- Hey, Ross. - Hey, Rachel.
乔伊·崔比安尼在吗
ls Joey Tribbiani here?
不在
Uh, no.
如果你见到他
lf you see him, will you please tell him
请转告他我在找他
that l'm looking for him...
这次我不会吐了
...and that this time l am not gonna throw up!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我  我很好
Me? l'm great!
我很好  我好得不得了
l'm fine! l'm so good!
但是你知道谁不好吗
But you know who's not great?
男人
Men!
-你是男人对吧  罗斯  -对
You're a man, right, Ross? - Yeah.
-坐下  -好
- Sit down. - Okay.
我问你一件事
Let me...let me ask you something.
婚誓对你们来说是个屁吗
Do wedding vows mean squat to you people?
为什么我们一说要出门  砰
Why is it that the second we tell you we are going out of town...
你们就跟邻居的遛狗小妹上床
...bam, there you are in bed with the neighbor's dog- walker?
我们很抱歉
We're sorry.
我说真的
No, seriously. Seriously.
婚姻的神圣性死哪儿去了
What has happened to the sanctity of marriage?
你昨晚不是才在乔伊家厮混吗
Didn't you spend last night at Joey's?
你是谁呀  侦探吗
What are you, a detective?
我不知道你和你丈夫怎么了...
Look, l don't know what's going on with you and your husband...
也希望那位遛狗小妹已经成年
...and what is hopefully an adult dog- walker.
但我要说不是全天下的男人都那样
Look, can l just say, not all men are like that.
有些男人愿意尽全力
There are men who'll do whatever it takes
只希望能挽回婚姻
to make their marriage work.
有些男人甚至愿意退到一边
And there are some men who will stand by and watch...
看老婆跟健身房刚认识的女人"2P"
as their wives engage in what can only be described as a "twosome".
火热得好像旁若无人
...with some woman she barely knows from the gym!
这些男人是谁啊
Who are these men?
就是我认识的一个人
Just men. A guy l know.
你可能要告诉他
Well, you might want to tell him
听起来他的老婆
it sounds like his wife...
是同性恋
...is gay.
她才不是...
She is not....
她是同性恋
She's gay.
天啊
Oh, my God.
她是典型的同性恋
She is so gay!
我真不敢相信
l can't believe this.
已婚者的"黄道吉日"啊
Good day for married people, huh?
很遗撼你老公不忠
l'm sorry your husband cheated on you.
很遗憾你老婆是同性恋
l'm sorry your wife is gay.
看来女人也没那么好
l guess women aren't that great either, uh?
去告诉我老婆啊
Try telling my wife that.
我可以进来吗
Okay to come in?
进来  吃饭  随你便
Yeah, come in, eat, whatever you want.
罗杰医生又被叫走了
Dr. Roger got beeped again.
我知道  你猜是谁找他
Yeah, l know. Guess who beeped him.
-什么  -我就是那个脾脏破裂病患
- What? - l'm the ruptured spleen.
你为什么要这样
Why would you do that?
因为你不该和他在一起
Because you shouldn't be with him.
你应该和我在一起
You should be with me.
是吗  对
Really? Yeah.
听你聊罗杰  让我好痛苦
When you were talking about Roger, that was killing me.
昨晚那件事不能过了就算了
Look, things like last night, they don't just happen, you know.
至少对我意义重大
At least not to me.
我跟另外两个女人在一起时
l mean, with the other two women...
共度春宵后  隔天早上
in the morning, you know, i was lying there
我就巴不得赶快去找朋友
l couldn't wait to go hang out with my friends.
但是跟你...
But with you...
我就是跟朋友在一起
...l was, you know, already with a friend.
-钱德  - 你知道你很可能不想跟我交往
- Chandler.. - I know you probably don't want to go out with me.
因为我太爱开玩笑
l make too many jokes,
也没认真谈过感情
l've never been in a serious relationship...
又不是个"医生"
...and l'm not technically a "doctor."
只有过一个女人  对不对
There was just one woman, wasn't there?
真的有两个
No, there were two.
-一个是我吗  -正确
- lncluding me? - Oh, yeah.
* 只要两次心脏病发 *
* It only takes two heart attacks *
* 就能让你认清 *
* to finally make you see *
* 一次死不了 *
* one of them won't do it *
* 但第二次会让你解脱 *
* but the second will set you free *
* 告诉你的恨意与愤怒 *
* Tell all your hate and anger *
* 是该道别了 *
* It's time to say goodbye *
* 我就会这么做 *
* And that is just what l will do *
* 只要我的老板们一死 *
* Soon as those bastards l worked for die. *